napw.com 2019-07-07

# International Association of Women (IAW) - Dream. Rise. Lead.

**_Please carefully review the following PRIVACY POLICY before using this website or any associated Services. Your use of the Services described below indicates your acceptance of these terms._ **

_Our PRIVACY POLICY applies to all activity occurring on this website (iawomen.com or iaw.napw.com), including all web pages on the domain, any related domains, or third-party domains hosting International Association of Women (IAW) intellectual property; the IAW bulletin boards; blogs; and other webinars; local chapter pages; members database(s); and internal or web-based e-mail submissions (“the Services”). By using the Services you: (a) warrant that you are competent to understand the terms; (b) warrant that you have read and understand the terms; (c) agree that the terms are valid, binding and enforceable; and (d) enter into a legal agreement with IAW, agreeing to abide by the terms during your use of the Services. If you disagree with any of the terms set forth below, you should not use the Services. Please be aware that IAW may amend the Privacy Policy from time to time, with all changes posted here. Your continued use of the Services further warrants that you accept any amendments IAW may make._

##  1\. STATEMENT OF COMMITMENT 

IAW is committed to protecting the privacy, reputations and dignity of its members, users and those who browse this website. Today, more than ever before, personally-identifiable information is at risk of malicious disclosure and misappropriation, particularly through online sources. IAW has invested heavily in many areas to prevent the misuse of information collected through operation of this website, the Services and Proprietary Information described in our Terms & Conditions, and stands behind this Privacy Policy as part of its corporate commitment to safeguard your privacy. 

As part of our commitment to you, IAW warrants that it will not misuse your personally- identifiable information that it collects through your use of this site, and that we use reasonable and suitable physical, electronic and managerial safeguards to protect such information. 

It is imperative that you read and understand this Privacy Policy. If you disagree with it, or refuse to abide by its terms, please discontinue use of this website. 

##  2\. WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT 

IAW collects certain personally-identifiable information, defined as information concerning a natural person which, by its nature, may be used to identify that person. For purposes of this Privacy Policy, this information is limited to that which is collected through this website or through membership in IAW. 

###  A. Personally-Identifiable Information 

The personally-identifiable information IAW collects may include: 

  * Both first and last name, used together
  * Social Security Number
  * E-mail address
  * Telephone Number
  * Home or business address, when it includes both a street and town names
  * Employer, job title and description
  * Demographic information such as postal codes, preferences and interests (when identifiable through other personally-identifiable information)
  * Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

While simply browsing our website, users generally remain anonymous. That is, the process of browsing alone does not lead to the collection of personally-identifiable information. However, members, other users and even browsers are sometimes asked to voluntarily provide personally-identifiable information in response to surveys, questionnaires or other features of the website. 

In addition, we collect personally-identifiable information from members throughout the membership process, and elements of such information are retained and can be found on the website through the basic member search function and where members are featured in public areas of the website such as through our VIP Women and Women in the Spotlight features. 

###  B. Cookies 

IAW also collects non-personally-identifiable information, generally pertaining to your browser and or computer, in the form of “cookies.” Cookies are small files which request your permission to be placed and reside on your computer’s hard drive, so that a web application might respond to you as an individual browser, tailoring the website’s presentation to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and storing information about your preferences. 

##  3\. HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT 

Keeping with our commitment to your privacy, reputation and dignity, IAW makes judicious use of the information we collect through your use of this website, and uses that information only to further the organization’s Mission and/or to enhance your browsing experience. 

###  A. Personally-Identifiable Information 

IAW uses the personally-identifiable information it collects through your use of this website to better understand your needs and to provide you with better service and an enhanced membership and/or browsing experience. Specifically, IAW may use the personally-identifiable information it collects to: 

  * Conduct internal record keeping
  * Maintain archives as required by law
  * Ensure the integrity of our member database
  * Conduct necessary transactions
  * Improve our products and services
  * Periodically send promotional e-mail to those who have provided an e-mail address, regarding new products, special offers or other information that may be of benefit to you
  * Contact you for market research purposes, via any of the contact methods you have provided
  * Customize the website according to your preferences and interests

As set forth in IAW’s Terms & Conditions, IAW reserves the right to use information collected in the membership process, associated with members’ basic profiles, as IAW sees fit. This may include the lease or sale of IAW’s membership list, which may include some or all of the biographical information members have provided when enrolling with IAW. 

Users’ acceptance of this Privacy Policy and IAW’s Terms & Conditions signifies their agreement to receive periodic e-mail communications from IAW regarding: 

  * Legal notices about changes to the Terms & Conditions or Privacy Policy
  * Legal notices about any security breaches involving your personally-identifiable information
  * Transactions with IAW or authorized and affiliated third-parties
  * Marketing or promotional events and/or organizational news

Please be aware that your membership in IAW and use of this website do not require that you accept such e-mail communications. Should you elect not to receive such e-mail communications, you may opt out by following the instructions **[HERE.](http://info.iawomen.com/hs/manage-preferences/unsubscribe-simple?via_redirect=true) **

###  B. Cookies 

As discussed, the IAW website uses cookies to help enhance your browsing experience. 

Specifically, we use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used and their frequency of use. This helps us analyze data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to our members’ and users’ needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis. It does not contain personally-identifiable information, and we do not retain this data beyond its analytical use. In addition, we use cookies to alert our website to your return visit, and the cookies help to identify your browsing preferences and track the pages you visit, all to enhance your browsing experience. 

Overall, cookies help us to provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor in a relatively anonymous way (no personal identifiers) which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you other than the data you choose to share with us. 

Please be aware that you have the option to decline the use of cookies. Most web browsers automatically “accept” cookies, but you may be able to either by alerted to or decline their use by altering your browser settings. 

##  4\. CONTROLLING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION 

Consistent with our commitment to your privacy, IAW takes reasonable physical, electronic and managerial precautions to safeguard your information. 

However, all information other than personally-identifiable information described above that you provide during the course of your use of the IAW website is considered non-confidential. Except as provided in this Privacy Policy or by applicable law, IAW disclaims any liability for the control of the non-personally-identifiable information you provide. Consequently, users agree that IAW has no obligations with respect to the non-personally-identifiable information users provide, and that IAW shall not be liable for any use of such information. 

Moreover, this website may link to pages, promotions or offers from third-parties which, if followed, may take your browser to a site controlled by a third-party. As IAW has no control over such sites or the information such sites collect, IAW specifically disclaims any knowledge of or liability for third-party sites’ collection practices. Before providing any personally-identifiable information to a third-party site (or any other website, for that matter), you are encouraged to locate and review the site’s Privacy Policy. 

If you believe that any of the personally-identifiable information IAW maintains about you is incorrect or incomplete, please e-mail us as soon as possible, at: membershipservices@iawomen.com or write to us at: 

Professional Diversity Network, Inc.   
801 W. Adams Street Suite 600   
Chicago, IL 60607 

##  5\. PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES/UPDATES 

_This Privacy Policy is effective from December 31, 2017 forward._

As the law of the Internet develops and threats to your privacy morph or new threats become known, it periodically becomes necessary to update or change this Privacy Policy. IAW hereby reserves the right to do so at any time. However, IAW will provide notice of such changes by highlighting the Privacy Policy page. We encourage all members, users or other visitors to frequently review this Privacy Policy, and your continued use of this website constitutes your acceptance of any changes or updates which may occur.
